They've broken through Area 9.
They're heading to Sector 10
through Corridor 117.
I knew Vitaly would be headed there...
Sector 11...
Liza...
Close all of the bulkheads!
Friends
Roger that!
Onii-sama?
Hey, Claire.
I thought you'd be wanting
to hear from me about now.
Leave Vitaly to me.
It's not like we don't know each other.
But, Onii-sama, Liza is...
Claire, trust in me.
Onii-sama!
Liza...
It sucks that they don't have a core.
Yeah, there's no real weak point.
Let's go.
You care for your friend, huh?
Submit to me.
You're nothing but tools.
Damn it...
They're not your tools or your slaves.
Know your place, automaton!
Wait!
Are you all okay?
Is your leg okay?
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
I'll get help here right away.
S-Sure.
Thank... you.
Liza Harvey.
Who would have thought
we'd see each other again here,
Vitaly Tynyanov?
Judar...
So you knew I'd come here.
From the beginning.
You knew I might be here too, right?
Yeah. You saved me
the trouble of finding you.
What are you trying to pull?
You know.
This is revenge.
You pretended to love me,
then used and discarded me.
You misunderstand.
Enough!
I'm going to destroy Liza
in front of your eyes
and sink the Little Garden.
First I'm going to show those Slayers
just how powerless they are.
Wh-What is this?
What in the world is this noise?
Detecting sound waves being emitted
from the replicants and the bee-types.
The whole ship is being affected.
It seems these sound waves
are targeted to hurt Slayers alone.
I'm emitting sound waves which act on the virus
that Slayers are infected with.
It's only a matter of time
before the Little Garden falls.
Impressive, Vitaly.
Your work is always beautiful.
If I said I wanted you again,
would you help me?
Don't mess with me!
I came here in order to
push you into despair.
Stop now.
You can still be saved.
This is the end, Judar.
No...
Why is she awake?
Do you remember Kirishima Sakura?
Kirishima... Sakura?
Liza reacted to her songs.
I made a little wager,
hoping she'd awaken faster.
I used you.
You calculated all of this, and even
put the Little Garden in danger...
Would I have any other reason
to see you again?
Again, you...
Judar!
Y-You damn monster!
How rude of you to address
my sister in that manner.
I thank you, Vitaly.
You have helped my plans
progress quite a lot.
I hate myself for being the slightest
bit happy after hearing that.
Sorry for waking you, Liza.
You can rest within the capsule.
We will talk again when the time comes.
No, Onii-sama.
I have something that I must do.
Hayato!
Emile!
Damn it!
I'm not going to let you!
If only I had the power...
The power to save everyone!
You do.
What was that?
You have your song.
Song?
Yes.
The power to drive this terrible noise away.
To drive it away...
Sing for everyone.
For the Little Garden.
I have my songs!
Now you'll be able to stand.
Karen-chan, let's sing for everyone.
Right!
Hundred On!
I can move?
These voices...
I can feel my strength returning.
Hey, is this...
Kirishima Sakura and Kisaragi Karen?
The singing from the concert hall
is canceling out the noise.
All Slayers are returning to action.
This is the power...
...of their song.
This is Sakura and Karen's...
I can fight now.
I only have one chance!
This ends now!
Trenta-class replicant down.
We have no casualties.
What happened to Kisaragi Hayato?
Kisaragi Hayato is at zero percent
energy remaining,
but there's no danger to his life.
You did well,
Kisaragi Hayato.
The Trenta-class replicant is reactivating.
It's still active.
What was that?!
Detecting a large amount
of energy from its head.
It's going to fire!
That's...
Nakri!
Nee-chan, take care of Nakri.
Vitaly!
I'm not letting you get away with this!
Krovanh!
Krovanh-kun!
Chris, I'm going out.
Take care of things here.
Claire-sama!
I have to save him.
I have to save him. I have to save him.
I have to save him! I have to save him!
Trace On!
She traced the replicant...
Nesat-chan...
This is bad.
Claire, can you hear me?
What is it, Char?
She's in the same situation
as when Liza went out of control.
At this rate...
It can't be!
She'll lose control of her energy
and cause a huge explosion.
Is there any way to stop her
from going out of control?
There is one.
What is it?
If we cease her vital function,
now that she's been absorbed by the replicant,
I imagine it'll stop it from happening.
Hayato...
Kisaragi Hayato...
You're...
Looks like we get to see each other again.
Oh, yeah!
Is everyone on the Little Garden okay?
Things are getting worse.
However, Kisaragi Hayato,
you might be able to save her.
I can... save her?
Please, save the Little Garden,
save that girl,
and save my sister.
Energy is increasing.
4,000... 6,000...
Claire-sama!
She isn't guilty of anything,
but I have a responsibility
as the captain of the Little Garden.
I will...
Please wait!
Kisaragi Hayato?
Please give me time to save Nesat.
What are you going on about?
The lives of thousands of people are at stake!
I know that.
But Nesat's life is just as important
as every one of those.
Understood.
However, I will end this when I have to.
Understood?
Thank you, President.
Hundred On!
Nesat, can you hear me?!
It's me!
Kisaragi Hayato!
Kisaragi... Hayato...
Little Garden...
Slayer...
Slayers are the enemy!
I won't say I understand the pain
and suffering you went through,
but one twist of fate,
and I might have become like you.
Slayer!
Enemy!
Save her.
I know you can do it, Hayato.
Emile...
Leave it to me.
Claire-sama, we have
less than three minutes now.
Did you hear that, Kisaragi Hayato?
You don't have any time. Hurry.
Nesat, listen!
You're free now.
You can live freely now!
Free...
The likes of Vitaly won't control you anymore!
I want to protect the Little Garden.
And I want to save you.
Believe in me!
Believe...
...in you...
It doesn't have to be me.
If there's someone out there
you can believe in,
then it can be them!
Please know we won't betray you!
Be...lieve...
Claire-sama, we can't hold out any longer!
Kisaragi Hayato!
Nesat!
Nesat, can you hear me?
Believe in us.
In the Little Garden.
Believe... in you...
Can I really trust you?
You can.
We're friends.
Friends...
Welcome to the Little Garden.
Hayato!
You did it, Hayato!
Yeah.
Nee-sama.
Thank you for protecting the Little Garden.
Liza!
Hey, Hayato.
A lot of things have happened
since we first came to the school.
Yeah.
A lot more is going to happen, I'm sure.
But I only want one thing.
Huh?
My wish is to always be with you.
Emile—
I'm Emilia right now.
Emilia... I want to be with you, too.
Who knew there was a place
like this in the school?
I get to train with Noah.
I'm sure the fireworks will be pretty.
E-Everyone...
I guess we're sorry for intruding!
N-Nii-san?
What are you doing?! You're both guys!
I... uh... that is...
That's enough, Kisaragi Hayato!
How dare you do that to the princess of
the glorious Kingdom of Gudenburg,
Emilia-sama!
H-Hey! Don't say that...
Huh? Princess Emilia?
Princess of Gudenburg?
Looks like I can't hide it anymore.
Emile...
I'm sorry for hiding it up until now.
My real name is Emilia Gudenburg.
I'm actually a girl and a princess.
What?!
A... a girl?!
A-And a princess?
A commoner and royalty.
Romantic, isn't it?
No, it isn't!
I told her not to do stuff like that...
P-President?!
I was wondering where you went,
and you were messing around here...
President!
Calm down!
As the captain of the Little Garden,
I can't let this be!
President, you dummy!